<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-12T18:53:56-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Christopher Banks</title><entry><title type="html">Online Cross Entropy Task Allocation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/01/Online-Cross-Entropy-Task-Allocation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Online Cross Entropy Task Allocation" /><published>2020-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/12/01/Online-Cross-Entropy-Task-Allocation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/12/01/Online-Cross-Entropy-Task-Allocation.html">&lt;p&gt;An online method for cross-entropy sampling is developed, used in multi-agent task allocation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/online_ce_experiment_run_simback.png&quot; alt=&quot;online_sim_back&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;abstract&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We present a task orchestration framework for multi-agent systems utilizing linear temporal logic (LTL) andcross entropy optimization, a stochastic optimization technique. We define task orchestration as a combination of taskdecomposition, allocation and planning for a robot or team of robots given a high-level specification. Specifically, weconsider  tasks  that  are  complex  and  consist  of  environment  constraints,  system  constraints,  or  both,  that  must  besatisfied. We first show this for the single agent case where transition systems for the environment allow tasks to bedeveloped as linear temporal logic (LTL) specifications. Trajectories are then generated via motion primitives for a singlequadcopter and optimized via cross entropy to ensure optimal satisfaction of a cost function. We extend this work to themulti-agent case where a team of homogeneous quadcopters are considered to satisfy an LTL specification. In orderto provide faster computations and initial cost agnostic sampling we formulate the online version of multi-agent taskallocation via cross entropy for tasks specified in temporal logic specifications. The results of this framework are verifiedin simulation and experimentally with a team of quadcopters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Journal Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>active</name></author><summary type="html">An online method for cross-entropy sampling is developed, used in multi-agent task allocation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Anomaly Detection In Auv Images</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/14/Anomaly-Detection-In-AUV-Images.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Anomaly Detection In Auv Images" /><published>2020-04-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-04-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/14/Anomaly-Detection-In-AUV-Images</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/14/Anomaly-Detection-In-AUV-Images.html">&lt;p&gt;Classifying and categorizing anomolous data gathered from a deep sea autonomous underwater vehicle (AUV).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/icefin_img.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;UAVML&quot; width=&quot;300px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a project completed Spring 2020 during the Machine Learning course at Georgia Tech. Our team acquired data from the IceFin AUV composed of 2,000 images of the Antartic seabed. We trained a CNN to classify images as either anomolous or non-anomolous. From this classified data, we used unsupervised machine learning algorithms to group similar images. See the full project as well as Github repo below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.christopherjamesbanks.com/ML_project/&quot;&gt;Project Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>past</name></author><summary type="html">Classifying and categorizing anomolous data gathered from a deep sea autonomous underwater vehicle (AUV).</summary></entry></feed>